jossip.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy - Jossip

Our privacy policy is pretty simple. We respect yours, especially because without it, we wouldn't be in business. Listen up.

When visitors come to a Jossip site, we collect standard information such as their IP addresses and referral data. We also collect information visitors voluntarily submit to us, such as their names, email addresses, mailing addresses, phone numbers, interests and preferences about our services, and other personal data. Generally this information is collected when visitors sign up for a user account, comment on our sites, initiative communication with Jossip, or enter a contest or promotion; none are required to visit or use a Jossip site.

We do not rent or sell your personal information. There are no "select third-party marketers" we give your information to without your expressed consent.

We do place cookies on your computer. Our cookies come may from our publishing system and our advertisers. Cookies help store your name or email address when commenting or logging in to a Jossip site. Our advertisers and our ad serving technology may place cookies placed on your computer for tracking purposes.

We do collect standard usage and tracking data, including IP addresses, page visits and session activity. This data, however, is not collected in a manner that can uniquely identify you. We collect it on aggregate and sometimes make that aggregate information available to advertisers.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

If you have any concerns, please write us at [publisher@jossip.com](http://www.jossip.com/).
